Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting,
either will I'm feeling alive,
look out below, wake up sunshine,
here we go.
Raise your flag up high,
hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky, time
to journey on, on your mark.
Come aboard with me.
We're on Earth, a legendary!.
If you can show your breath?
Then we'll make some waves!.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners!.
Cause if you're wanted?
Then you're a winner!.
For we are on the cruise.
And freedom is the only rule!.
Fearless night and day.
Cause that's just our way!.
Find one piece.
I'll be the first.
I've heard it be so bad just at first?.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel.
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting.
In the world I'm feeling alive.
But I'll be loud!.
Wake up sunshine, here we go!.
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end!.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!.
I've always got your back, my friend!.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed?.
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In the world I'm feeling
alive, look out below!.
Wake up, sunshine!.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!.
We go!.
Many years ago.
For some unknown purpose,
there were three powerful entities
that could destroy this entire world.
They were ancient
weapons named after gods.
Pluton, Uranus, and Poseidon.
And one of those great
weapons is the princess.
Indeed.
Well, if that's the case, we can't
let anyone else know about this.
If we did,
the government and every other organization
would want Shirahoshi for themselves,
not to mention other pirates.
Ancient weapons?
Strong enough to destroy the whole world?
To think I was just going to take off
after stealing all the silly trinkets!
How foolish of me!
I almost overlooked the most
valuable item they've got!
That mermaid princess is more
precious than I imagined.
Tell me something, Luffy!
Why you sit here stuffing your face?
Are you aware of all that's
been happening in the world?
Where you getting that, Jinbei?
Ah, so you're completely uninformed?
That's a problem, but I
can't say I'm shocked!
I'm lost.
We brought you more pets, Luffy.
Come with me.
Sure.
Just give me a second.
I'm gonna take this one to go.
Hey!
You guys left the party, too?
I'm trying to sober up.
I drank too much.
And I ate too much.
Sanji flirted too much.
This place is so magical.
There's so many babes.
I can't take it.
What?
Chalaka, Inu, and Aokiji
fought each other?
It was a major event.
Did Rayleigh never mention this
to you during your training? Nope.
This is news to me.
That was cruel of him.
Oh, I knew about it the whole time.
So did I do good? That's crazy!
It all started two years ago,
right after the war ended.
Sengoku resigned as fleet admiral.
Aokiji was well liked among his own men,
so Sengoku nominated him
to take over the title.
But many high ranking officials favored
Aka Inu, so he became a contender as well.
Aokiji is normally cool tempered,
but he was quite adamant in
his disapproval of Aka Inu.
He found him unfit for the position,
so it did not take long
for the disagreement
to come to blows on an island somewhere.
It was the first and final
battle between the two admirers.
It was agreed that whoever lost would
withdraw his candidacy without protest,
and the winner would become.
the leader of the Navy.
As the rest of the world now knows,
they fought for 10 whole days.
The two opponents were equally matched
in power, But the duel finally ended.
Akainu, or as some know him,
Sakazuki, emerged victorious.
That bastard won!
I'm putting an end to this!
So did he kill Aokiji?
Well, both admirals were severely injured.
In fact, Aokiji couldn't
even stand after it was over.
However, Akainu was strangely
merciful towards him.
Despite this, Aokiji refused
to accept the result.
He has resigned from the Navy.
I can't believe Aokiji would
just up and quit like that.
Indeed.
I wonder what's been going
through his mind since then.
The government has certainly
lost a valuable asset.
They have found ways to
overcompensate in Aokiji's absence.
One might argue that they're
more dangerous than ever now.
There is still much you do not know.
Listen closely.
Before you reach the new world,
you must be aware of two key
changes that have occurred there.
Now then, the first matter, as
I've already begun to explain,
is that the Navy under Fleet Admiral
Sakazuki is stronger than before.
And secondly, the Blackbeard Pirates
are making strides of their own.
Those guys again?
You mean the ones we met back in Mocktown?
They attacked my homeland.
I can never forget them.
Long time no see, Straw Heck, Luffy.
He spent many years as a member
of the Whitebeard Pirates.
He was already familiar
with the territory,
so after their captain died,
Blackbeard wasted no time in
seizing control of it for himself.
Using the Tremor Tremor fruit he
stole upon Whitebeard's death,
he's gaining quite the reputation
along with shanks kaido and big mom he's
joined the ranks of the four emperors so
he stole whitebeard's Devil Fruit and his
title talk about a scumbag i agree his
audacity is infuriating there's a rumor
going around that they're currently on the
hunt for those with Devil Fruit powers i
am not sure how it's possible but it seems
they found a way to acquire abilities
from the other people upon killing them
clearly they plan to usurp the strongest
powers they can find and become unstoppable
be on your guard no they're gonna
take mine the human human fruit i think
you're safe i worry for you the most luffy
I know there's a great deal of
bad blood between you and teach.
You must take care
Luffy
Have you been listening to me?
You're supposed to be the captain here.
The captain needs to have at
least some idea of the situation
Whoa, it's okay. Gene Bay.
The rest of us heard you Huh?
I thought the captain was supposed to
goof off while the crew looks out for him.
Shame on you, Luffy.
A good captain dedicates his
life to the safety of his crew.
And here you are.
Don't be such a drag.
I'd rather take my chances
and see what happens.
It's more fun that way.
I don't envy you all one bit.
Tell me about it.
The party's for you, you know.
Why are all you guys hiding out?
Hey, Kuma.
Oh, yeah.
What happened to Weepy Hachi?
She leave?
She was tired.
All the excitement made her need a
little nap, so she went up to her room.
Hang on. Zoro? Sanji?
It seems like there's
some kind of monster here.
You may be right.
Yeah, I feel it too.
You cut me to the quick princess.
I promise I won't do
anything to cause you pain,
my dear!
I was ready to settle for just the treasure
after selling off the other mermaids;
turned out to be a hassle.
But you might just be an exception?
Now then I want you to be a good girl
and go to sleep for a little while.
Can you do that for me?
I just received word from my brother.
He and the crew have made port on
fish man island We're all headed
to the new world and we'd like
for you to come along with us.
Now now show me a smile.
Hey, you! It was you!
Luffy!
Ah!
Oh!
That guy was still here.
Luffy!
That was scary!
Thank you for saving me!
Luffy, you lucky bastard!
I should have kicked him
while I had the chance!
That was a close call.
We really can't thank you enough, Luffy.
It's no big deal that
ruffian who stole from us.
I can't believe he was still nearby
This place is usually locked up
so tight even a guppy can't get in
but with everything that's happened?
It seems we left it open and look that big
tower over there has
been sliced clean in two!
The robber must have done it
while we were out in the plaza.
Sorry, actually that
would be this guy man.
You should have seen him
when they got out of the
cage He was hacking and
slashing all over the place.
Learn to keep your mouth shut!
Stupid starfish.
I don't think so!
If I don't say something
that makes me an accomplice?
Hey, righty.
Here's a question
Righty you mentioned a
treasure thief right?
Yes You heard correctly that
unsavory man who is just here
snuck into the palace and robbed
us blind really well then?
You're gonna let him steal national treasures
now that my people are safe from harm!
I care nothing for material riches.
Oh, cut the crap.
Wait, so you're saying you
don't want them anymore?
If you can rescue them,
you're free to keep them.
It's the least I can do for our heroes.
Well, if you insist.
You idiots just had to kick
him into next week, didn't you?
Why couldn't you just knock him
out and tie him up in the tower?
Oh, Nami, you're so cute.
Go catch him and bring him back.
Your majesty, it's hoarding his men, sir.
Their handcuffs came off. But how?
Damn you humans!
Don't think we've forgotten our grudge.
We'll exact our revenge soon enough.
It's your head will be the first to die.
Bring him to my cell!
Oof, my back hurts.
I sure could use a drink.
I age myself on purpose.
I want to get back at the Straw Hats,
but my energy's at an old time low soon.
We won't show them an ounce of mercy.
What in the world has happened here?
Don't tell me.
Is that Heart and his crew?
You think these guys can hold me?
What a bunch of morons.
I'll break them and -
Captain Horny!
Why are they so brittle?
Just as I thought!
That energy steroid you were
taking to make yourself stronger!
And the pill from inside the tamate box!
They're one and the same, aren't they?
Uh, tamate box?
A priceless artifact passed
down for generations, Jamal.
The pills hidden inside were
highly valuable as well,
but ten years ago someone
stole them from us.
We failed to catch the culprit.
His Majesty was concerned that a scandal
might break out, so we closed the case.
Actually, Heart, I think that happened
around the same time you left the army.
Interesting.
Of course it was me.
Look what's happened to my body!
Need me to spill it out for you?
The pills were treasured. Air logs.
The truth behind their
purpose, lost long ago.
Tales of Their power and
the curse that accompanied
them were both passed
down merely as legend.
But still enough to make us wary.
It would appear that our
discretion was warranted.
However
However, the tomate box was carefully
guarded for the safety of our people.
This result is truly regrettable.
If you had not allowed your judgment to
be clouded by foolish dreams of power,
you would not have subjected
yourselves to this terrible fate.
Wh-What the hell do you know?
In any case, they'll never
get their vengeance now.
You'll see the heavens have chosen us to
settle the score and
that's just what we'll do.
Then we'll not only
wipe out the human race
we'll annihilate you
and your entire family!
I pity them perhaps I ought
to offer them clemency.
You're a disgrace to our
people Fishman Island
is healing now the least that you can do.
is refrain from speaking.
I don't want the children
hearing your poisonous words.
Minister of the Left! Huh?
Baron Tamago and Mr. Pecum's.
They're at the sweets factory.
They're here to collect for Big Mom.
We can't face them now.
We don't have any sweets
for this month's payment.
Heart and his lackeys
tore the factory apart.
And all the candy we
could salvage was sent to
the banquet so the Straw
Hats could enjoy it.
What should we do?
Something tells me Big Mom of the Four
Imperates won't be satisfied with an apology.
That a woman would level an
entire country for sweets.
After much celebration, the
banquet finally comes to an end.
They're seriously going to
let us keep all that treasure?
Cool!
That's pretty generous.
Do you think Luffy and the
others are all right, Mommy?
I'm so worried.
Eh, they're fine.
We're going to be fancy
rich pirates now! Woo!
It sounds nice, but something tells me
this is too good to be true. Hey, Usopp!
Why don't we go look for
the treasure thief, too?
Uh, how about no?
I found out that guy's
bounty is over 200 million,
so he's not going to be an easy target.
Whoa, and mine's only 50 berries.
Hey, Zoro, Sanji, check it out.
Easiest treasure hunt ever.
That one punch knocked him out cold.
I almost feel bad for him.
And he left all this loot
sitting out in the open.
Neptune's going to let us keep all this?
I guess he really is as goofy as he looks.
Awesome.
How much meat do you think this will buy?
I think his body could hold all this.
I mean, I know he's made
a sludge. But still.
One, two, three.
Let's take it back to the palace. How?
We need a flying fish.
Which way to town, Zoro? That way.
Or we could always run off with the loot.
What?
Well, minister of the left,
please have mercy, Mr. Peckham.
Heart and his crew attacked the factory,
and now we don't have any candy left.
And what makes any of that our problem?
You're supposed to pay us some candy each
month in exchange for using Mama's name.
Don't tell me you've forgotten
about our little agreement?
And I was planning on taking
some sweets for myself.
which means now I'm mad and hungry.
We've done business with you for a long
time, so I hate to say this, but...
I don't think I need to remind you how
scary Mama can be when she's angry.
She'll kill you!
Look at those cute little eyes!
You'd better pay up! Right now!
What's going on?
Hey, this is the candy factory
Papa Goo told me about. Yeah?
Hopefully we can find a
flying fish around here.
This must be the place where they
make that candy I like so much!
Hey, guys, are you going
to give us the grand tour?
Ho, ho, Straw Hat Luffy.
Oh, my God, hi.
Like, is the banquet over?
Luffy, why is he here? Uh-huh.
Dude, I totally pigged out, too.
Fishman Island's got all kinds of delicious
food, but that candy was unbelievable.
Oh, my God.
What's that?
Whoa, whoa, which day on the empty cave?
Don't say anything! Oh!
Hey, it's Mr. Catfish! What are you up to?
They said candy.
Just who is this guy?
Huh.
That's dry hat Luffy, no doubt about it.
He's got no business here.
He's a pirate, right?
Well, sorry, you see...
Listen here, kid!
Tell me what candy you're talking about!
I can explain, Mr. Pickles. Actually...
Hey, I don't know you.
You're not a fish man.
Are you here for sweets, too?
I'm right there with you, buddy.
I can't get enough of them, either.
You what?
All right, that's it.
Evaporate to say what I think he said.
Well, I assure you there's
an explanation. Awesome.
I've never seen a talking lion.
It's no big deal.
We have a fluffy animal
guy, too. Ah, kiss!
Here comes...
Threatening this monsieur will not bring
us any closer to the sweets, mon frere.
The tea party is in four days.
Let us try to avoid a Foxy pas.
If we have to wait here until
morning, well, c 'est la vie.
You're just as weird as
he is. What's your name?
Bonjour, enchanté,
mes amis Pirates Je Zeus Baron Tamago,
I am pleased to make your acquaintance
Tamago?
Oui, take care to remember
my name, s 'il Vice plaît
Now, excusez-moi, messieurs
Am I to comprend that you have
devoured all the sweets in the factory,
my little bon vivant?
Did you get that?
Yep, that was me.
I could go for some more right about now.
Unfortunately, the candies
have met their denouement.
Attends,
that is the jolly roger of
our boss, Charlotte Lin-Lin,
also known as Big Mom
of the Four Emperors.
That symbol indicates that this
island is Mama's territory, d 'accord?
You see, mama owns the place.
Which means fishman island is
under big mom's protection.
That's a nice thing to do!
I like your boss already.
Kinda weird name, though.
Au contraire, mon ami.
This is a business deal.
Huh?
We allow them the protection
of our mark And in exchange,
they have to pay Mama 10
tons of sweets every month.
That's a lot. Oui, monsieur.
There is nothing in this world
Mama loves more than sweets.
Mama says sweets from Fishman Island
are like creme de la creme, you know.
Pay up tomorrow, and
we will bid you adieu.
I'm sorry, sir, but I told you before.
The machinery used to make
the candy was badly damaged.
It'll take us at least two
weeks to make the repairs.
We won't be ready tomorrow.
That is not our problem,
monsieur. Hey, fancy!
Why can't you just wait a while?
Yeah, why doesn't your boss have the
balls to come talk to us himself?
He's one of the four emperors, isn't he?
Well, your manners.
Our leader happens to be a madame
pirate and a fearsome one at that.
That said, I do not think Mama
has the balls. It's a girl?
That's different, then.
I love sweets.
I just can't resist the things.
And I really love men who can make them.
Anyway, what if your boss
lady doesn't get her candy?
In that case...
Fall!
The deal is off.
The big mom parrots will attack on Mars.
And you can say so long and
bonsoir to this island miserable.
You want to destroy the island?
How crazy can you be?
You can't do that over
some stupid candies.
I won't let you.
We just saved this place, you know.
You seem so happy, Mama.
Yes, it's only four days
until the tea party.
I can hardly wait.
I'll finally be able to taste those
delectable candies from Fishman Island.
I'm so excited my stomach is already
producing all the acid I'll need.
Candy, candy, Fishman Island candy.
I see you are all excited too.
Of course, Mama.
That's the best candy there is.
Then wait for them in my stomach, because
that's where they're all going to go.
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh,
oh.
Mama!
I'm home now!
Oh, Bobbin, how did your mission go?
I set the whole place on fire!
That's wonderful to hear.
That country's baked goods
were the best in the world.
I bet it smelled so
delicious as it burned.
It's a shame we had to do it.
But they should have honored our agreement
Can I have a snack?
If they can't pay in sweets,
they pay with their lives.
There's one thing I can't
stand, it's a broken promise.
That, and bitter candy, of course.
Oh, that reminds me, apparently Fishman
Island can't send their payment right now.
Peckholms just told me all about it.
Should I burn that down, too?
I want my Fishman Island sweets!
Get those fools on the
Transponder Snail now!
I already told Mama Gah!
She's probably calling in to check on us.
Really? No!
Not Big Mom, she's scary!
You talk to her, Egghead.
She isn't going to like this at all.
Yeah, what's up?
Who is this?
It's Big Mom, right?
What are you doing? Stop!
You don't sound like Tamago or Peccoms.
Who is this?
My name is Monkey D. Luffy.
Soon to be king of the pirates.
Was all that really necessary?
Oh, no, Luffy.
Nice going.
Monkey... D?
So you must be Garp's grandson.
I remember you, young man.
You're the little upstart who
interfered with the war two years ago.
There's no more candy! Huh?
They can't send you any!
So I heard correctly.
They're supposed to have ten tons.
Will I eat it all?
It's gone now! Ah!
Don't you lie to me you stupid child you'd
better not be covering
for those weak fishmen.
I'm not lying it was all me I didn't
know they were supposed to be for you.
I'll make you a deal we've
got a bunch of treasure
if I give it to you then
can we call it even?
Seriously?
What?
I can't eat gold and diamonds, can I?
Sweets are the only treasures
that mean anything to me.
One minute, monsieur.
Are those really full of treasure?
Yeah, they are.
Pardonnez-moi, maman.
Let's think about it, no? City alors.
Only a few short days ago.
That enfant terrible,
Captain Kidd, took down Dieu of
our allies specials, n 'est-ce pas?
It was a disaster!
We suffered a major
financial setback and we
could certainly start
the monetary assistance.
And no candies are your eyes
on it, but if you ask more,
the best option is to accept the treasure
in lieu of sweet payments for now.
You'll only have to wait a couple of
weeks to collect your confections, Dakar.
If you really want something sweet,
we can always pick up some
bonbons for you on the way back.
Huh?
Do you even hit yourself top of me?
I don't think you even
suggest something like that!
What kind of poor excuse for a pirate
compromises on what she wants most? Oi!
Please forgive me, Mama!
Be that as it may.
This insolent pirate who ate
all my sweets intrigues me.
Forget Fishman Island.
Now that you've chosen to go against me!
I'll just have to get my
revenge on you instead.
Well then, Monkey D.
Luffy
Now that I know who you are.
Come here!
Let's chat in the new world.
She means to kill him?
Sure thing, be there soon.
I've got something I need
to settle with you, too.
I like this island.
It's too risky to trust you with it.
Once I get there, I'm gonna kick your ass.
And then I'll make Fishman
Island my territory.
Little brat